Guide to the Stanford University, Feminist Studies Program, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH.2002-304
  - Susan Matisoff, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Michelle Rosaldo, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Adrienne Rich, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - FS 102: Course Development, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Lisa Layne, Circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Fem Studies, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - OAIV Search, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Sarah Bryer, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Dominique Bloom, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Laura de Ney, 1994 Apr (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Melissa Feinberg, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Heidi Hentila, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Karie Youngdahl, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Misc., 1990-1992 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Carin Anderson, 1993 May (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Patricia Bowlin, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Jae Choi, 1993 Mar (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Melissa Feinberg, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Karin Gaisford-Kissain, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Alison Herrold, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Mary Pratt, 1990 Jul (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Margaret Hodder, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Patricia Lambie, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Jessica Levine, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Kelly O'Neill, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Racquel Stote, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Jennifer Teaford, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Kim Walsh, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Leslie Yang, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - 1993 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Juliet Crider, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Oona Ceder FS 101 TA, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Gordana Crnkovic, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Susan Dever, 1988-1992 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Linda Garber, 1992-1993 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Kim Gillespie, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Transfer of Expense, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Transfer of Expense, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - SU--25 Rapid Purchase Orders, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - SU--34B Check Requests, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Expense Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Check Requests--SU34B, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Petty Cash, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Various Expenses (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - SU--10 Purchase Requisitions, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - University Store Orders, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Transfers of Expense, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Transfers of Expense, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - SU--13 Interdepartmental Requests, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Copy Center Orders, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Check Requests--SU 34A, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Rapid Purchase Orders, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Transfers, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Expense Reports, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Purchase Requisitions, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Copy Center, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Bookstore Requests, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Book Store Requisition, 1981-1987 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - 1985-1986, Misc (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Petty Cash, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Petty Cash, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - Petty Cash, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Petty Cash, 1980-1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Services, 1982-1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - SU--10 Purchase Requisitions, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - SU--25 Rapid Purchase Orders, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - SU--25 Rapid Purchase Orders, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - University Stores Orders, 1988-1991 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Telecommunications, 1982-1986 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - SU 34b -- Check Requests, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Transfer of Expense, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Delivery receipt, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Bookstore Requisitions, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Book Adoption Forms and Information, 1985-1991 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Copy center orders, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Cashier Deposits, Circa 1990 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - SU-13 Interdepartmental Requests, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Expense Reports, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Expenditure Statements, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Expenditure Statements, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Expenditure Statements, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Expenditure Statements, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Expenditure Statements, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Expenditure Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Expense Reports, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Funding Requests, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Funding Requests, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - SPO Newsletter, 1987 Sep (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Grants and Funding, 1993-1996 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Funding Proposals, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Funding Requests, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Elaine Chang, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Lee Medovoi, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Kamala Viswesaren, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Judith Raiskin, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - 1991-1992, Teaching Assistants (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1988-1989 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Teaching Assistants, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Teaching Asst Applications FS 101, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Visiting Scholar Applications, 1990 Dec (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Visitors, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Pnina Geraldine Abir-Am, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Gloria Bowles, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Caroline Bynum, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Jean Davison, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Hortensia Allende, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Juliet Mitchell Visit, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - End of Quarter Report, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1983-194 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - End of Quarter, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - End of Quarter Report, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - End of Quarter Report, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - End of Quarter reports, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - End of Quarter Reports, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Autumn Quarter, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Helen Longino, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Catharine A MacKinnon, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Sherri Marie Matteo (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Toril Moi, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Cherrie Moraga, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - New Courses, 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Confidential, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Martha Roldan, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Esther Rothblum, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Zeljka Svrljuga-Saetre, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Visiting Professors, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Londa Schiebinger, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Edna Spitz, 1984-1988 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Barrie Thorne, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Elizabeth Wilson, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Claire Johnson, 1988-1989 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Melanie Lynth, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Marie Bott, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Karen Nymus, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Susan Reinhold, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Julie Widman, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Ann Bannerjee, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Sarah Bryer, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Andi Frisch, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Noel Hanrahan (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Julie Yuen, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Distribution Requirements, 1991-1992 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Michelle Cliff & Adrienne Rich, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Jeanne Barkey, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Elizabeth Britton Budd, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Dayna Lyn Goldfine, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Elizabeth Hoffman, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Anne Akers Johnson, 1982 Nov (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Betsy Jelliffe, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Laura Kay, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Eva Lohrer, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Jennifer A. McKnight, 1981-1987 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Stephanie Marie Poggi, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Elizabeth Powell, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - 1981-1986 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Caroline Streeter, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Jennifer Wakefield Wilson, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Diana Akiyama, 1991-1993 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Susan Groag Bell, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Alice Bach, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 72)